Effective Date: 8th June 2023

1. Introduction

This Privacy Policy outlines how Scammer.info (“we,” “us,” or “our”) collects, uses, and protects the personal information provided by users (“you” or “your”) when accessing and using our website. We are committed to safeguarding your privacy and ensuring the security of your personal information. By accessing and using Scammer.info, you consent to the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

2. Information We Collect

2.1 Personal Information

When you use Scammer.info, we may collect personal information that you voluntarily provide to us. This may include your name, email address, IP address, and any other information you choose to provide when interacting with our website or community features.

2.2 Non-Personal Information

We may also collect non-personal information automatically when you visit Scammer.info. This may include your device type, browser information, IP address, and other technical information related to your use of the website. We may use cookies, web beacons, and similar technologies to collect this information. You have the option to disable cookies in your browser settings, but please note that this may impact your experience on our website.

3. Use of Information

3.1 Archival, Research, and Educational Purposes

The primary purpose of Scammer.info is to provide a platform for users to share information about scams, scammers, and fraudulent activities. We collect and process personal and non-personal information to maintain an archive of scam-related content, conduct research and analysis, and provide educational resources to help users identify and combat scams effectively.

3.2 Crime Tackling Purposes

We may use the information you provide on Scammer.info to assist law enforcement agencies and other relevant authorities in their efforts to combat online fraud and criminal activities. We may share relevant information with these entities to aid in investigations and the prosecution of offenders.

4. Disclosure of Information

4.1 Content and User Actions

Scammer.info is a user-generated content platform, and we are not responsible for the accuracy, legality, or safety of the information posted by users. Any content you voluntarily provide or post on our website may be publicly accessible, and other users may access and use this information. You should exercise caution and refrain from sharing any personal or sensitive information that you do not want to be disclosed publicly.

4.2 Third-Party Service Providers

We may engage third-party service providers to assist us in operating our website, analyzing user data, and delivering relevant advertisements. These service providers are obligated to maintain the confidentiality and security of the information we provide to them and are restricted from using it for any other purpose.

4.3 Legal Compliance and Protection

We may disclose your information if required to do so by law or if we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary to comply with legal obligations, protect our rights and property, investigate fraud or illegal activities, or protect the safety of our users or others.

5. Data Security

We employ reasonable security measures to protect your personal information from unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. However, no data transmission over the internet or electronic storage system is entirely secure. Therefore, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

6. Third-Party Services

6.1 CloudFlare

We use CloudFlare for Domain Name System (DNS) services and content delivery to optimize the performance and security of Scammer.info. CloudFlare may collect and process certain information as described in its privacy policy. We recommend reviewing CloudFlare’s privacy policy to understand how your information is handled by them.

6.2 Google AdSense

Scammer.info uses Google AdSense to display advertisements. AdSense uses cookies and similar technologies to serve relevant ads based on your browsing behaviour. These cookies may collect non-personal information about your visits to Scammer.info and other websites to provide targeted advertisements. Please review Google’s Privacy Policy and Ad Settings to learn more about their data collection and use practices.

7. Children’s Privacy

Scammer.info is not intended for children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from children. If you believe that we have inadvertently collected personal information from a child, please contact us, and we will take immediate steps to delete such information from our records.

8. Changes to this Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to update or modify this Privacy Policy at any time. We will notify you of any material changes by posting the updated policy on Scammer.info. Your continued use of the website after any modifications to the Privacy Policy constitutes your acceptance of those changes.

9. Contact Us

If you have any questions, concerns, or requests regarding this Privacy Policy or our practices concerning your personal information, please contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://scammer.info/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

Please note that this Privacy Policy applies solely to Scammer.info and does not govern any third-party websites or services linked from our website. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of those third parties to understand their data practices.

Powered by [Deez Nutz](https://scammer.info/), best viewed with JavaScript enabled
